http://www.daniel-swarovski.com/en-US/s-californiaprivacy/

CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
Your Rights Under the California Shine the Light Law (Cal. Civ. Code Section 1798.83)
California residents are permitted to opt out of the disclosure of their personal information, as defined in Cal. Civ. Code 1798.83 (e)(7), to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To opt out, email us at
us.privacy@swarovski.com or call us at +1 800-426-3088.
We will not disclose the personal information of California residents who have opted out to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.
Your Rights Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)
California law requires businesses to disclose information regarding the rights of California residents pursuant to the CCPA. Any terms defined in the CCPA (Cal. Civ. Code Section 1798.140) have the same meaning when used in this section.
California residents may request that we disclose to them the following information covering the preceding 12 months:
­	- The categories of personal information we have collected about them;
­	- The categories of sources from which the personal information was collected;
­	- The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling personal information;
­	- The categories of third parties with which we share personal information;
­	- The categories of personal information about them that we have sold and the categories of third parties to which the personal information was sold;
­	- The categories of personal information about them that we have disclosed for a business purpose and the categories of third parties to which the personal information was disclosed;
­	- The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about them.
A California resident may request the disclosure of the information listed above by calling +1 800-426-3088, submitting a request at
us.privacy@swarovski.com, or submitting a request at one of our retail locations.
Such a request may be referred to as a right to know request.
Pursuant to California law, we will verify the California resident’s identity before complying with any such request, which may include confirmation of the California resident’s name, email address, a recent purchase, and other information, as well as the California resident’s submission of a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that they are in fact the California resident whose personal information is the subject of the request.
To assist us in complying with your request, please provide your full name, email address, postal address, and Swarovski Club member number and/or Swarovski Crystal Society member number (if applicable) in your request, and provide information regarding a recent purchase (identify item, location where purchased, and approximate date).
Please be aware that if we cannot verify your identity from the information we already maintain, we may require additional information from you to verify your identity prior to complying with your request.
Such additional information will be used only for the purposes of verifying your identity and for security or fraud-prevention purposes, and will be deleted as soon as practicable after processing your request.
If we are unable to verify your identity to the requisite degree of certainty, we will not be able to process your request and will so inform you and explain why.
A California resident has the right to request that we delete any personal information about the California resident that it has collected from the California resident, and that we direct any service provider to delete such personal information from its records. Such a request may be referred to as a request to delete.
However, pursuant to the CCPA, a California resident’s personal information may not be deleted under certain circumstances, including where maintenance of your personal information is necessary to: complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected, fulfill the terms of a written warranty or product recall conducted in accordance with federal law, to provide a good or service that they requested or that is reasonably anticipated within the context of their ongoing business relationship with us, or to otherwise perform a contract between Swarovski and you; to detect security incidents, protect against or prosecute fraudulent or illegal activity; to enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with their expectations based on their relationship with us; to comply with a legal obligation; or to otherwise use their information internally in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which they provided the information.
For more information about these and other situations in which we may not delete a California resident’s personal information, please see Cal. Civ. Code Section 1798.105(d).
A California resident may request the deletion of their personal information by calling +1 800-426-3088, submitting a request at us.privacy@swarovski.com,
or submitting a request at one of our retail locations. Before deleting a California resident’s personal information, we will obtain confirmation that the person wishes to have their personal information deleted and verify their identity, as required by the CCPA.
Verification may include confirmation of the California resident’s name, email address, a recent purchase, and other information, as well as the California resident’s submission of a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that they are in fact the California resident whose personal information is the subject of the request.
To assist us in complying with your request, please provide your full name, email address, postal address, and Swarovski Club member number and/or Swarovski Crystal Society member number (if applicable) in your request, and provide information regarding a recent purchase (identify item, location where purchased, and approximate date).
Please be aware that if we cannot verify your identity from the information we already maintain, we may require additional information from you to verify your identity prior to complying with your request.
Such additional information will be used only for the purposes of verifying your identity and for security or fraud-prevention purposes, and will be deleted as soon as practicable after processing your request.
If we are unable to verify your identity to the requisite degree of certainty, we will not be able to process your request and will so inform you and explain why.
A California resident may use an authorized agent to submit a right to know request or a request to delete.
To use an authorized agent, the California resident must provide the agent with written authorization.
In addition, the California resident may be required to verify their own identity with us.
We may deny a request from an agent that does not submit proof that they have been authorized by the California resident to act on their behalf. Such requirements, however, will not apply where a California resident has provided the agent with power of attorney pursuant to Cal. Prob. Code Sections 4000 to 4465.
In the preceding 12 months, we have collected the following categories of personal information about California residents from the following sources and for the following purposes.
The CCPA requires that we refer to specific categories of personal information enumerated in the CCPA.
We may collect only certain pieces of personal information described in a given category and may not collect certain pieces of personal information described in each category.
In the preceding 12 months, we may have disclosed for a business purpose the following categories of personal information about California residents to the following categories of third parties (to the extent the disclosure was made to a third party).
Category of Personal Information Collected
Category of Source of Collection
Business or Commercial Purpose of Collection
Category of Third Party to Which Personal Information May Have been Disclosed for a Business Purpose
Identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number; driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers
•	You
•	Our customers
•	Business partners
• Automated Collection from website visitors
•	Service delivery
•	Research & Development
•	Marketing
•	Advertising
•	Authorities and others
Categories of personal information described in subdivision (e) of Cal. Civ. Code Section 1798.80 (Any information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with, a particular individual, including, but not limited to, his or her name, signature, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, driver's license or state identification card number, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information)
•	You
•	Our customers
•	Automated Collection from website visitors
•	Service delivery
•	Marketing
•	Advertising
•	Research & Development
•	Compliance & Operations
•	To create anonymous, aggregated or de-identified data
•	Affiliates
•	Advertising partners
•	Service-related third parties
•	Professional advisors
•	Authorities and others
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (Profile data which is optional: gender and/or age)
•	You
•	Our customers
•	Automated Collection from website visitors
•	Service delivery
•	Marketing
•	Advertising
•	Research & Development
•	Compliance & Operations
•	Affiliates
•	Advertising partners
•	Service-related third parties
•	Professional advisors
•	Authorities and others
Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
•	You
•	Our customers
•	Automated Collection from website visitors
•	Service delivery
•	Research & Development
•	Marketing
•	Advertising
•	Compliance & Operations
•	Affiliates
•	Advertising partners
•	Service-related third parties
•	Professional advisors
•	Authorities and others
Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer's interaction with an internet website, application, or advertisement
•	You
•	Business partners
•	Automated Collection from website visitors
•	Service delivery
•	Research & Development
•	Marketing
•	Advertising
•	Compliance & Operations
•	Affiliates
•	Advertising partners
•	Service-related third parties
•	Professional advisors
•	Authorities and others
Swarovski does not sell your personal information as that term is defined under the CCPA.
We will not discriminate against a California resident because the California resident exercised any of their rights under the CCPA, including, but not limited to, by:
- Denying goods or services to the California resident;
- Charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties;
- Providing a different level or quality of goods or services to the California resident; or
- Suggesting that the California resident will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
However, we may charge a California resident a different price or rate, or provide a different level or quality of goods or services, if that difference is reasonably related to the value provided to us by that resident’s data.
In addition, we may offer financial incentives, including payments to California residents as compensation, for the collection of personal information, the sale of personal information, or the deletion of personal information.
We may also offer a different price, rate, level, or quality of goods or services to the California resident if that price or difference is directly related to the value provided to us by that resident’s data.
We will notify California residents of such financial incentives and. we will enter a California resident into a financial incentive program only if the California resident gives us prior opt in consent which clearly describes the material terms of the financial incentive program, and which may be revoked by the California resident at any time.
We will not use financial incentive practices that are unjust, unreasonable, coercive, or usurious in nature.
We currently offer the financial incentives listed below:
Financial Incentives Program
Summary of Financial Incentive and Material Terms
Categories of Personal Information Implicated
Opting into Financial Incentive
Withdrawing from Financial Incentive
Swarovski Club
Swarovski Club Rewards are determined based on a minimum purchase value that a member reaches through his or her purchases in a 12-month period.
•	No minimum purchases required to reach the “bronze” level and receive the following benefits: collection trend and style news; invitations to pre-sales, and a 15% off birthday voucher.
•	Spend $250 within 12 months to reach the “silver” level and receive the following, additional, benefits: access to exclusive jewelry products; invitations to VIP events; and free standard shipping.
•	Spend $600 or more within 12 months from reaching the “silver” level to reach the “gold” level and receive the following, additional benefit: loyalty gift.
•	Identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number; driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers
•	Categories of personal information described in subdivision (e) of Cal. Civ. Code Section 1798.80 (Any information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with, a particular individual, including, but not limited to, his or her name, signature, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, driver's license or state identification card number, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information)
•	Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (Profile data which is optional: gender and/or age)
•	Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
Sign up for Swarovski Club online or in-store
Send an email to
customer_relations.us@swarovski.com; or call our customer service team at +1 800 426-3088
Click here to view the Swarovski Privacy Policy
Follow us:
Join the Swarovski Club to subscribe to the newsletter and receive a 10% voucher for your next purchase on swarovski.com
7 characters min. / include a numeric digit
By clicking the "Join the Club" button I agree to join the Swarovski Club and I confirm that I have read and accepted the General Terms and Conditions. I understand that my data will be processed according to the Swarovski Privacy Policy.
JOIN THE CLUB
Already a Swarovski Club member? Login here
$(this).closest('#scFooterRegistrationFormConfigWrapper').find('.js-scFooterRegistrationFormConfig')
.formValidation({
autoFocus: false,
framework: 'bootstrap',
icon: {
valid: null,
invalid: null,
validating: null
},
fields: {
'values[scFooterRegistrationFormDefinition_email]': {
trigger: 'blur',
validators: {
regexp: {
regexp: /^[a-zA-Z0-9.!#$%&'*+/=?^_`{|}~-]+@[a-zA-Z0-9](?:[a-zA-Z0-9-]{0,61}[a-zA-Z0-9])?(?:\.[a-zA-Z0-9](?:[a-zA-Z0-9-]{0,61}[a-zA-Z0-9])?)+$/,
message: 'Please enter a email address.',
message_en: 'Please enter a email address.'
},
notEmpty: {
message: 'Please enter a email address.',
message_en: 'Please enter a email address.'
},
stringLength: {
message: 'The number of characters for this field must be between 0 and 70',
message_en: 'The number of characters for this field must be between 0 and 70',
min: 0
,
max: 70
},
}
},
'values[scFooterRegistrationFormDefinition_password]': {
trigger: 'blur',
validators: {
callback: {
callback: function(value, validator, $field) {
var messages = [];
var messagesEN = [];
var errorOccured = false;
if (!value.trim().match(new RegExp('(^$|^(?=.*[0-9])(?=.*[A-Z]).{7,}$)', ''))) {
messages.push("The Password has to be at least 7 Characters long as well as contain one Number and one capital Letter.");
messagesEN.push("The Password has to be at least 7 Characters long as well as contain one Number and one capital Letter.");
errorOccured |= true;
}
if (errorOccured) {
return {
valid: false,
message: messages.join("<br/>"),
message_en: messagesEN
}
} else {
return true;
}
}
},
notEmpty: {
message: 'Please enter a password.',
message_en: 'Please enter a password.'
},
}
},
}
})
.on('success.field.fv', function() {
/* note: we need to check if there is an error in the form, as the plugin does a validation on field level.
Validating the whole form on blur of a field is no option, as the customer does not want to see error messages on all fields
when entering one field. In case of an error on at least one field we disable the submit button manually */
var $form = $(this).closest('form');
if ($form.find('.form-group.has-error').length > 0) {
var $button = $form.find('.js-button');
if (!$button.hasClass('disabled')) {
$button.addClass('disabled');
}
}
})
.on('err.field.fv', function(e, data) {
if(data.element.closest('.form-combo-molecule').length){
/* Get the messages of field */
var messages = data.fv.getMessages(data.element);
/* Get the error message content of the field */
var errorContent = data.element.closest('.form-combo-molecule').find('.errors');
/* Get the hidden error message of the field */
var errorField = errorContent.find('small[data-field="' + data.field + '"][style="display: none;"]');
/* Loop over the messages */
for (var i in messages) {
if (errorField[1] == undefined) {
var newErrorContainer = document.createElement("small");
$(newErrorContainer).attr("class", "help-block");
$(newErrorContainer).attr("data-field", data.field);
$(newErrorContainer).attr("data-fv-validator", "callback");
$(newErrorContainer).attr("data-fv-for", $(data.element[0]).attr("name") );
$(newErrorContainer).attr("data-fv-result", "INVALID");
$(newErrorContainer).attr("data-tracked", "true");
$(newErrorContainer).html(messages[i]);
if (errorContent.text().includes(messages[i])) {
$(newErrorContainer).hide();
}
errorContent.append(newErrorContainer);
}
}
}
})
.on('success.field.fv', function(e, data) {
/* Remove the field messages */
$errorContent = data.element.closest('.form-combo-molecule').find('.errors');
$errorContent.find('small[data-field="' + data.field + '"]').remove();
$errorContent.find('small[data-fv-result="INVALID"]').removeAttr("style");
})
.on('success.form.fv', function() {
var formId = 'scFooterRegistration';
if (!formId || formId === 'cfRequest' || formId === 'cfResponse') {
formId = 'scFooterRegistrationFormDefinition';
}
ACC.tracking.pushFormSubmit(formId);
});
var replaceDatePatternWithValue = function(mandatory, fieldConfigCode, fieldConfigPattern) {
var date = fieldConfigPattern.toUpperCase();
var year = $("#" + fieldConfigCode + "_year").val();
var month = $("#" + fieldConfigCode + "_month").val();
var day = $("#" + fieldConfigCode + "_day").val();
date = date.replace(/[Y]+/, year);
date = date.replace(/[M]+/, month);
date = date.replace(/[D]+/, day);
var hiddenDateField = $('.js-' + fieldConfigCode + '_hidden');
if (mandatory) {
hiddenDateField.val(date);
} else {
hiddenDateField.val(date == "" ? "" : date);
}
};
var triggerFormValidation = function(fieldId, mandatory, fieldCode, dateFormat) {
replaceDatePatternWithValue(mandatory, fieldCode, dateFormat);
$('.js-fieldCode').formValidation('revalidateField', 'values[fieldCode_'+ fieldId + ']');
};
var removeDateMoleculeError = function(molecule) {
if(molecule.hasClass('has-error')){
molecule.removeClass('has-error');
molecule.find('.help-block').find('span').remove();
}
};
dispatcher-check
Brand
Since 1895, founder Daniel Swarovski’s mastery of crystal cutting has defined the company. His enduring passion for innovation and design has made it the world’s premier jewelry and accessory brand.
Discover more
SWAROVSKI CLUB
Access many sparkling rewards includings birthday surprises, priority access and exclusive sales to VIP invitations.
LEARN MORE
SWAROVSKI CRYSTAL SOCIETY
Join the exclusive world of brilliance and live your crystal passion to the fullest.
Copyright © 2020 Swarovski. All rights reserved. SWAROVSKI and the SWAN logo are registered trademarks of Swarovski AG.
Copyright © 2020 Swarovski. All rights reserved. SWAROVSKI and the SWAN logo are registered trademarks of Swarovski AG.
Your browser blocks cookies, please enable cookies and reload to continue using the website.
